Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflec
  - Subseries 23: Fieldwork
    - Nuba of Talodi, Southern Kordofan, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1576 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Dar Zaghawa, Northwest Darfur, Kutum, Umberu, Kornoy, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 7 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1577 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Dar Zaghawa, Northwest Darfur, Kornoy, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1578 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - East Jebel Marra at Sunni and Ta'isha Baggara in South Darfur, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1579 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Beni Halba, zeffa, Eid el Ghrenem, South Darfur Baggara, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1580 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Beni Halba Baggara at Eid el Ghrenem in South Darfur, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1581 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Fur of Girri - West Jebel Marra, Darfur, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1582 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Haddendoa Beja, Red Sea hills and Tokar, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white. 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1583 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Haddendoa Beja, Red Sea hills and Tokar, 1967, 1 contact sheet: black and white, 35 mm; 6 negative strips: black and white, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1584 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Subseries 24: Photo album
    Received as a photo album with magnetic pages. The contents were documented in the album before removal. They are listed below in original order, although the numbering does not reflect this. PH1688-PH1757 were taken in Darfur.
    - Map of Sudan and neighboring countries, photograph of a map; AFC 2012/008: PH1809 (Box 5)
    - Map of ethnic groups in Sudan, photograph of a map; AFC 2012/008: PH1810 (Box 5)
    - Roxane McCollester and the wife of the Shertai of Kornoy at sacred stone shrine, 1 photograph: Kodachrome print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1585 (Box 5)
      PH1585 and PH1586 mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption: "Always present are the problems of terrain and transportation to reach informants." See PH1804 for similar image.
    - Roxane Connick Carlisle in a desert landscape, standing on the rocks, 1 color print (Kodachrome); 3 1/2 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1586 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1585. The mat has the lab-stamped date May 1967.
    - Zaghawi area, near Khartoum, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1587 (Box 5)
      PH1587-PH1591 were mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption for these photos: Scenes of Darfur, province in west Sudan.
    - Zaghawi: area near Khartoum, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1588 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1587.
    - Man crouching by a vehicle, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1589 (Box 5)
    - Waterfall, Suni; Geb. Marra Darfur, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1590 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1587, and PH1447, PH1448, PH1739, and PH1799 for similar images.
    - Desert scene, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1591 (Box 5)
    - Near Kassala, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1592 (Box 5)
      PH1592-PH1596 mounted on the same page.
    - Butana desert, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1593 (Box 5)
    - Merowe, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1594 (Box 5)
    - Eastern slopes of Jebel Marra, at Suni, Darfur, 1967. Fur homes, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1595 (Box 5)
    - Creek [?], 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1596 (Box 5)
    - Haddendoa of Red Sea hills near Tokar, Sudan, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1597 (Box 5)
      PH1597-PH1599 were mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption for these photos: "Usually in Sudan you take whatever transport is available or you walk."
    - Near Suakin, Haddendoa area, Red Sea hills, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1598 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1597.
    - Dar Zaghawa near Kornoy, Darfur, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1599 (Box 5)
    - Men pushing a truck, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1600 (Box 5)
      PH1600-PH1604 were mounted on the same page.
    - People standing by a truck, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1601 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1600.
    - Roxane and four men standing by a jeep, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1602 (Box 5)
    - Roxane standing by a jeep, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1603 (Box 5)
    - Roxane standing by a plane, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1604 (Box 5)
    - Darfur; Horse racers near Zalingei, Western Jebel Marra, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1605 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1605-PH1607: Kordofan: the tribal Bederiya of North. These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Bederiya, Kordofan, Rep. Sudan, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1606 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1605.
    - Bederiya; Nazir's bodyguard, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1607 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1605. Note on the verso of this image: "I was allowed to inspect the bridles encrusted with silver and semi-precious stones"
    - Roxane and two people with two camels, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1608 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1608-PH1610: "Red Sea hills near Tokar - Haddendoa Beja." These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Roxane and one person standing by a kneeling camel, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1609 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1608.
    - Roxane and one person standing by a camel, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1610 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya, Kordofan, Rep. of Sudan, 1967, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1611 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption: "The following pages show the village environment and musicians of Arabic tradition in Kordofan, Sudan Republic, 1967."
    - Rebab, Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/8 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1612 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1612-PH1618: "Bederiya of Abu Haraz, Kordofan. Men play gerin horn and rebab chordophone." These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Rebab, Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1613 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1612.
    - Gerin player, Abu Haraz, Kordofan, Bederiya tribe, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1614 (Box 5)
    - Rebab, Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1615 (Box 5)
    - Gerin player, Abu Haraz, Kordofan, Bederiya tribe, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1616 (Box 5)
    - Gerin (cow's horn) player, Abu Haraz village, Kordofan province, Sudan, Bederiya tribe, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1617 (Box 5)
    - Gerin player, Abu Haraz, Kordofan, Bederiya tribe, January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1618 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya, Kordofan, Rep. of Sudan, 1967, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1619 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1619-PH1624: "Nahass drums brought from Hejaz over 500 years ago by Bederiya." These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Bederiya Nahass: tribal drums over a 1000 years old from Arabia brought into Sudan as the people migrated to Kordofan centuries ago from the Hejaz, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1620 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1619.
    - Bederiya, February 1967. Horsemen wearing coats of mail like the Crusaders and ancient Saracens, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1621 (Box 5)
    - Roxane with recording equipment slung over one shoulder, and surrounded by people, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 6.; AFC 2012/008: PH1622 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya, Kordofan, Rep. of Sudan, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1623 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya Nazir's horsemen and Roxane, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1624 (Box 5)
    - Daluka drum (center), two shetem drums (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1625 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1625-PH1626: Two small shetem drums accompany daluka drum while singing. These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Daluka drum (center), two shetem drums (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1626 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1625.
    - Daluka drum (elbow played), two small shetem drums (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1627 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1627-PH1628: Bederiya women use an elbow technique while playing daluka. These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Daluka drum, being played with one elbow and hand slapped (Abu Haraz village, in Kordofan province, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1628 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1628.
    - Dinger water and gourd idiophone (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1629 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1629-PH1631: "The dinger is used to accompany dura harvest songs among Bederiya women of Abu Haraz, Kordofan." These photos were mounted on same page.
    - Dinger water and gourd idiophone (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1630 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1629.
    - Dinger water and gourd idiophone (Abu Haraz village, Bederiya tribe, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1631 (Box 5)
    - Mortar and pestle used to grind dura during the singing, 1967, 1 color print; 3 1/2 x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1632 (Box 5)
    - Geneina, wife of the High Nazir of the Bederiya of Kordofan, Sudan, 1967. Song specialist with unique memory, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1633 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya schoolgirls dancing for me (Abu Haraz, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1634 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1634-PH1637: "Bederiya schoolgirls imitating their older sisters in the "dove" or "neck" dance. Kordofan province, Sudan, 1967." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Bederiya schoolgirls learning "dove dancing" (Abu Haraz, Kordofan, Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1635 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1634.
    - Schoolgirls dancing (Abu Haraz, a Bederiya tribal village in Kordofan, Republic of Sudan), January 27, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1636 (Box 5)
    - Bederiya male relatives encourage women dancers by clapping, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1637 (Box 5)
    - Two men wrestling; cow stands at far right (partially obscured), 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1638 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1638-PH1342: "Hamar villagers in northern Kordofan, 1967." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Hamar and El Obeid Information Ministry officer checking village gun (Kordofan, Sudan Republic), February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1639 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1638.
    - Thatched huts, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1640 (Box 5)
    - Hamar village scene (Kordofan, Sudan Republic), 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1641 (Box 5)
    - Hamar and El Obeid Information Ministry officer checking village gun (Kordofan, Sudan Republic), February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 1/2 in. x 5 1/2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1642 (Box 5)
    - Drummers playing, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1643 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1643-PH1646: "The Nazir of the Hamar of Kordofan with Nahass drum set brought from Hejaz centuries ago." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - A man, with drums behind him, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1644 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1643.
    - Drummers playing, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1645 (Box 5)
    - Four drums displayed against a wall, on a cloth spread on the ground, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/2 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1646 (Box 5)
    - Hawazma tribal dancers at Fershaiya village near Dilling in Central Kordofan, Republic of Sudan, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1647 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1647-PH1649: "Hawazma Baggara cattle nomads of central Kordofan sing lengthy epics, use clan drum codes, few instruments." These photos were mounted on the same page as PH1650-PH1651.
    - Hawazma tribal seat, Fershaiya [?] village near Dilling, Central Kordofan, Republic of Sudan, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1648 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1647.
    - Man holding two spears, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1649 (Box 5)
    - Fellata musicians entertaining their sponsor patrons of Hawazma tribe in Fershaiya [?] village near Dilling, Central Kordofan, Republic of Sudan, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1650 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1650-PH1651: Fellata migrants attached to a village settled by Hawazma Baggara, Fershaiya, central Kordofan. These photos were mounted on the same page as PH1647-PH1649.
    - Fellata musician at Fershaiya [?] village near Dilling in Central Kordofan, Sudan Republic, February 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1651 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1650.
    - Man playing an umkiki, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1652 (Box 5)
      Accompanying captions for PH1652-PH1656: "Arabized Nuba, Kadugli area, central Kordofan. Umkiki - one string chordophone used to accompany long "dobeit" epics. Pirimbiri lyre and ndon gourd and stick accompany dances." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Man playing an umkiki, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1653 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1652.
    - Group of people, one carrying a flag, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1654 (Box 5)
    - Man playing a ndon gourd, surrounded by other people, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1655 (Box 5)
    - Two men: one playing a ndon gourd and another playing a pirimbiri lyre, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1656 (Box 5)
    - Musicians playing nahass drums, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1657 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1657-PH1658: nahass drums of Arabized Nuba at Mirai Berra, South Kordofan - 1967. These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Close-up view of nahass drums, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 1/4 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1658 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1657.
    - Man wearing a headdress, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1659 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1659-PH1660: "The following pages show the settlement environment and musicians of non-Arabic tradition in the Nuba Mountains of South Central Kordofan, Sudan, 1967." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Man playing a horn, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1660 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1659.
    - Children standing by a hut, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1661 (Box 5)
      Accompanying caption for PH1661-PH1664: "This was my home and recording site during the dura harvest season with women of Katcha jebels in Southern Nuba mountains." These photos were mounted on the same page.
    - Village scene, with hut, women working, and truck in the background, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1662 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1661.
    - Basket, in various degrees of being filled, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1663 (Box 5)
    - Young woman standing in profile, with long braids, wearing Western dress, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1664 (Box 5)
    - Unfinished hut cluster drying in sun prior to heavy season of rain. One family live [sic] in many huts, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1665 (Box 5)
      PH1665-PH1668 were mounted on the same page.
    - A soldier with gun for shooting game to provide food for five of us at Talodi region settlement, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1666 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1665.
    - Tree trunk [?], 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1667 (Box 5)
      PH1665-PH1668 were mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption for PH1667-PH1668: When no game was available fried termites and baked dura bread were fine.
    - One side of hut cluster [?], 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1668 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1667.
    - Two women standing by a drum, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1669 (Box 5)
      PH1669-PH1671 were mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption: "Salara Valley Nuba use kira wrestling drums to encourage their champions. Drums may be individually owned by athletes who allow their friends to play their kira between bouts."
    - Man holding a staff, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1670 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1669.
    - Two drums, on the ground, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1671 (Box 5)
    - Wrestler's drum or amba used by Katcha Nuba of South Jebels, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1672 (Box 5)
      PH1672-PH1675 were mounted on the same page. Accompanying caption for PH1672 and PH1674: "Wrestler's drum or amba used by Katcha Nuba of South Jebels."
    - A kuniang from Salara Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1673 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1672. Accompanying caption for PH1673 and PH1675: "Lyres of widely separate Nuba groups have distinct playing techniques and similar string tuning patterns."
    - Man holding a short staff in one hand, and two small objects in the other, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1674 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1672.
    - Two men; one holding a perambera from Katcha Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1675 (Box 5)
      See the notes for PH1672 and PH1673 v.
    - Kujur's drum Meki, from Toum-Toum, Talodi, believed to cause death when sounded indoors, two players, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1676 (Box 5)
      PH1676-PH1680 were mounted on the same page.
    - Kujur's drum Meki, from Toum-Toum, Talodi, believed to cause death when sounded indoors, two players, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1677 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1676.
    - This Kujur is a manipulator of spirits, and a singer of ritual supplications, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 3 3/4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1678 (Box 5)
    - The meki drum never accompanies dance / tomoroleh flute is used alone or with feriferi lyre, Toum Toum, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1679 (Box 5)
    - The meki drum never accompanies dance / tomoroleh flute is used alone or with feriferi lyre, Toum Toum, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1680 (Box 5)
    - Kwi (a type of aerophone) used for wrestling, funeral assembly, hunting signals, Talodi and Katcha Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1681 (Box 5)
      PH1681-PH1684, and PH1808 were mounted on the same page.
    - Bursa (a type of aerophone) used for wrestling, funeral assembly, hunting signals, Talodi and Katcha Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1682 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1681.
    - Sorrow (a type of aerophone) used for wrestling, funeral assembly, hunting signals, Talodi and Katcha Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1808 (Box 5)
      See the note for PH1681. PH1808 was numbered out of sequence.
    - Kwi (a type of aerophone) used for wrestling, funeral assembly, hunting signals, Talodi and Katcha Nuba, 1967, 1 photograph: black-and-white print; 4 in. x 5 in.; AFC 2012/008: PH1683 (Box 5)